I have a lot of controversial opinions,
but this one could be top.
I think high ticket sucks, and
if you're a coach being told you need to
charge
thousands for your services,
you're being brainwashed and you're
actually being puppeted for someone else's
agenda.
But before we get into that,
some of my other controversial opinions,
knife and
fork,
90% of people eat the wrong way around.
You go to a Michelin star restaurant,
you've got to swap the knife
and fork around.
We'll get into that later.
I think you should run a mile
if someone's Hinge bio
says, "My most controversial opinion
is that pineapple belongs on a
pizza." It's called a fucking Hawaiian.
It's got a name for it, it's so common.
You're not funny. That person's chat
is going to be drier than Gandhi's
flip-flop.
I also think that people on benefits
shouldn't be able to vote.
What did he say?
And when it comes to immigration,
[laughs] well,
you're going to need to give me three
pints of Guinness before I
truly tell you that.
And no,
I will not tell you why Nigel Farage
follows me on Instagram.
In this video,
I'm going to give you everything you need
to know about high ticket
coaching, and hopefully,
it's going to empower you to understand
what to do with
your business a bit better.
And here's something else,
I welcome you to
challenge me.
We've got the comment section below.
Let's fight it out.
But to do so,
I just ask you to do one thing.
Watch the entire fucking video,
you mouth-breathing plebs.
Everything you're about to hear could be
biased. I don't do anything high ticket.
I don't, I never have.
So as a personal trainer, gym floor,
Bracknell,
2014 to about 2017,
charged between £25 and £40 an
hour.
Started an online service of about £40 a
week.
Got to a position where I hit maximum
capacity in mid-2017,
had to scale.
Had the option of going high ticket.
I had 50,000 Facebook followers.
Instead,
created an app called the James Smith
Academy.
We've had over 600,000 people through the
doors, made eight figures in
revenue, but because the bottleneck
was me, either I'm terrible at business,
but I looked at that and I thought, right,
what's going to be more congruent with
scaling my business and my brand,
me charging people thousands for
coaching, but they still need me,
or me bringing the prices down and
bringing other people in to service their
needs?
Because ultimately, the avatar,
the person, the problems that they have,
they don't
need me, they trust me. So
if they trust me, they can use my
coaches, my system, my philosophy, and
if they don't like it, they can have their
money back.
I have moved on from being a personal
trainer.
None of you will have seen me promote my
coaching app in months, maybe
years.
I still get paid every single week with a
significant
dividend that pays for my cars
and my mortgage.
The reason being is not only did we build
something pretty good, but our clients
have been with us for years.
Once you've been building a business on
the premise of
monthly recurring revenue at a sensible
amount that they can go, "Yeah, I'm just
going to keep paying that." We don't
promote the business.
Me and other James
are still making a living from it.
Is it Adam Sullivan levels?
No. Taylor Atcina's? No.
But here's the thing I really want to
drive home.
The backbone of any successful person
or personal brand is a
lifestyle business. And to me,
high ticket and
lifestyle are not congruent,
which means they can't live together, if
you're from Essex.
High ticket really arose in the pandemic,
and
people made millions from it,
and it wasn't so much the coaches, it
was the people
coaching the coaches.
We all know who they are.
Because all of the verbatim of arguments
that I'm getting in with people, it's
almost as if they're following a script,
and I know the scripts have come from the
same five business coaches. My books
were super low ticket.
I would spend a year writing a book.
Fair enough,
I got paid six figures advance for every
single one, but I make about
£1 a book.
So I'm going on these huge promotional
cycles, doing events, selling out
the Hammersmith Apollo,
having thousands of people come to it.
But I make 100K from the event.
Sounds amazing.
50K goes to the Hammersmith Apollo just in
the rent.
Plus, you've got the AV
and everything else.
But the book was a super low-ticket play.
Got me on "Good Morning Britain." I'm
arguing with Piers Morgan on TV.
Where so many people could have arrived
and gone, "James, you've got hundreds of
thousands of followers.
You could train people for £1,000 a
month." I went, "How
about give me £1 and I'll give you a
year's work?" Because the connection you
make
with someone once they've read your book,
that's six hours of listening, or however
many hours of reading.
They've connected with me whilst they're
on holiday, whilst
they're on a long-distance flight,
whatever it is.
Even the event in London,
the Hammersmith Apollo,
3,500 people in a room.
It's about £35 a ticket.
We could have charged more, but it
was more about having
people there. For me,
everything's a brand play,
not a profit play.
We could have charged 60.
We could have walked away with some
meaningful cash from
the event and maybe not sold out every
single row.
Now,
just before we get into my business
mentorship and the costs that I charge for
that,
the main reason I don't like high ticket
is I do not want anyone
to own me.
It's why I've never done a paid post,
never done a promotional post in
my life,
because the second a brand comes along
and says, "James, here's 100
grand," they can now control what comes
out my mouth, and that to me is bullshit.
If I want to say that ginger people
are lairy, or use the word retarded,
I don't
want some brand coming along going,
"James, you can't say that word." I charge
about 3K max USD for my mentorship,
and the reason I chose that amount,
it's what I paid Ed Lawrence.
And the reason that I can charge that,
I still think that's mid-ticket.
Three grand people can make back very
quickly. It's a return on investment.
That's why I'd consider
that not a substantial investment.
When I did Ed's course, I paid him 10,
so I paid for the 3
grand course,
then 10 hours of coaching on top.
So it's $1,000 a call.
Within six weeks,
I'd made my entire investment back
and also my
business paid for that, not me personally,
which is why I think personal training
high ticket is a farce, a facade,
because your client,
some can write it off through their
business, sure, but the majority of them
cannot,
and you're talking about post-tax income.
And ultimately,
you're selling something
that does not have a tangible return on
investment. I made the point that you
are someone's cheerleader, and a lot of
coaches are like, "I'm not a cheerleader.
I've got a cert three in fitness,
and I've done an S&C degree."
It's a workout. And respectfully,
the sooner you can appreciate that you are
just really giving someone a sequence of
exercises that they were going to do
anyway, some accountability,
a bit of cheerleading,
and ultimately you can be a
voice of reason in their mind
that they can respect,
the sooner you can scale your
business. So what's amazing here,
three grand for me seems like a fair
amount so I
can pull some profit from the business.
I can do some paid ads to acquire new
business.
Also,
so I can pay coaches within my mentorship.
I've got Ollie, my YouTube strategist.
I'll put a little picture of him here.
Got Cam, my marketing right-hand man.
He answers questions before me with
exactly what I would say.
And we even got Jayden, actually, who
was one of my students
that impressed me so
much, I've hired him. Cam and Jayden
are students that I've been really, really
impressed with, to the point I said,
"Do you want a job?" And
when you consider we
get 12 months of Discord within that,
it's like $300
a month to get access to four experts
and all the resources that I built for
lifetime access.
And I have a money-back guarantee within
my mentorship.
Now, me refunding someone three grand
is fine, but if this was 10 or it was 20
Which a lot of business coaches charge.
I may not be able to do
that so much because my emotional
connection to that would
be killer.
You've got something called loss aversion,
where the psychological pain
of losses is twice as bad as your
equivalent gain.
To explain that, if I'm walking along
and I lose a tenner, I am
way more upset than I would be happy
if I found a tenner.
The more you charge for coaching,
high ticket, the more inclined you are to
eat shit with a client
that you know isn't right because you just
don't want to
give up the money. Also,
when you do high ticket,
your volume of people that you
work with comes down.
So one bad egg contributes to a much
larger
percentage of your revenue for the month.
So you're getting rid of one client,
you've just lost 10% of your rev.
For me,
losing someone on 3K could be between one
and
5% acceptable losses.
If you only work with a really small
subset of clients, you lose one, it
is a pain, financially, emotionally.
I then tried high ticket, and I hated it.
Basically,
we were charging £2,000 for the
mentorship.
I was like,
"Wouldn't it be good from a price
anchoring perspective to have
something for £10,000?"
And all I wanted to do
was make the £2,000 look cheaper.
I thought, what we'll do,
we'll chuck in 10 one-to-one calls.
We sold 10 in a day without promoting it.
And I thought, "Sweet,
that's 100K." I said,
"Move it to 12K." We sold one more.
I said,
"Take this thing offline." Because
although the revenue was sweet, I've got
to do 10 hours with people. Each person,
that's 100 hours of
calls. So straight away,
what seemed like an amazing offer,
I'd take off.
Now,
just because someone's paid me £10,000,
I'm like, "We need to email them
straight away. They've just paid £10,000.
I have to get them on a call." I don't
particularly want to do 6:00 PM,
but they've
just paid £10,000,
so I jump on a call at 6:00 PM.
I loved working with the people
that I did on the high ticket,
but I also hated it
at the same time because my diary
was now owed to people for
money that I didn't really want.
My value is a freedom.
I love freedom.
If you just care about money,
maybe disregard this video
altogether. Today,
there's nothing in my diary,
not one thing, and
that is where I perform my best.
My missus, my fiancée, she says to me,
"What are
you doing today?" I just say,
"Work," because I've got no idea what I'm
doing
today. I'm in a creative mode.
I'm going to make a YouTube video.
I'm going to make short-form content.
I'm going to film some ads.
I'm have my second can of tonic
and lock in.
But the second I did high ticket
and there was two calls in my diary,
I thought,
"Jesus Christ,
these people have paid $1,000 each for
these calls.
I have to be [clapping] fucking on it." I
would be so focused on giving people the
best $1,000 ever because there
was a money-back guarantee on every call.
I gave 100 and fucking 50% to each call.
It exhausted me,
and I started resenting my work a bit
because the
$1,000, I could've canceled it,
I could've refunded everyone,
but the price point
was too high.
And that's maybe on me being an emotional
person. I don't know.
But even now, if I
was to charge for a one-hour call,
I'm sorry, but it would
probably be £3,000,
mainly because I don't want to do it.
I don't. I don't like phone calls.
The one-to-ones you're seeing on this
channel
that are coming live,
I gave them to people as part of an
incentive to buy
into one of my mentorship offers
that we had.
So when I jump on that call,
I can be chill.
I arrived at one five minutes late the
other day.
I said sorry, but ultimately, it's free.
Don't worry about it. Soz.
And sometimes in the mentorship,
I'm not going to lie to you,
someone's a bit rude
in the Discord, I'm like, "Fuck off.
Who the fuck do you think you're talking
to?
You only paid me £3,000, brother.
I know £3,000's a lot of money, but it
is not
enough money to be rude to me." I love
seeing the revenue go out my stripe.
I'm like, "See you." But if that
was £10,000,
I might be willing to be a bit of a
mug to keep it. So let's go back to 2021.
I had friends very close to me
that bought into this high-ticket coaching
model.
They say, "James,
I just made £2,000 on a phone call."
£2,000.
I'm like, "Selling what?" "Coaching.
12 weeks." I'm like, "What?
Let's do the maths on that.
It's £200 a week, brother." "Yeah.
High ticket." And I was like, "Right.
That's impressive.
It's a lot more than I'm making." James
Smith Academy is like £50 a month.
So I was like, what
are they getting for £2,000
that I'm getting for 150
quid? Now, I've realized it
was quite a high-pressure sales call.
And if you don't believe me,
look at the forms
that these coaches put in.
What is the goal that you want? What
are the repercussions of not hitting your
goal?
How long have you wanted to do this for?
You think it's like a readiness
questionnaire,
but it's part of the sales call
process. Yeah, but the thing is, Amanda,
you said if you didn't lose this
weight that you wouldn't look good for
your wedding and that the repercussions
would be you wouldn't look the way you
wanted to for the most important day of
your
life. Is that right, Amanda? Fuck that.
For £2,000.
Now, those coaches that did that,
five years later are still in the trenches
trying to make money.
If you cracked the meta of high-ticket
coaching,
why are you still doing what you're doing?
It didn't work because you found the top
1% of your
audience that actually
were just your top fans,
and they got a little bit
emotional on the call. They're like,
"Oh my God,
I really look up to this creator.
I'm loving their content." Then you put
the pressure on them.
And I'm sorry to say it,
I think a lot of you took the piss
and used your place
of authority to squeeze people for money
they didn't really realize wasn't worth it
until the end.
But British people especially
are too polite.
You could give me the worst haircut ever,
and at the end, I'm going to say, "Yeah,
it was amazing. Thank you so much.
Thank you so much.
Cannot wait to come back."
When in reality, I leave and I go,
"That's the worst
barber I've ever been to." So why
is it that this came from
trickle-down from mentors at the top?
Well, I'll tell you.
Everyone's got an audience,
and they've got a red-hot part of that.
And if you get the red-hot nucleus of it
and you get them on a call and you
high-pressure them for an hour with a
sales script, you will close them for any
amount of money that you want.
Then the mentors
that these people hired would
find that person.
They'd take six months' revenue
and close it
all in a week. And
that six months' revenue could've been 20,
30K.
Then what the coach will say is,
"Here's John.
He was making 2K a month,
started working with me, 20K a month.
I've 10X'd his revenue." No, no, no.
You've not just 10X'd his revenue.
You've taken the next six months' revenue
and squeezed it into this position.
Now, one,
you are manipulating the numbers to make
it seem like you are better at
doing what you're doing. This
is me talking to the business coaches.
But number two, the other reason here
is a lot of marketing
practices for people, coaches,
personal trainers, whatever,
is based on the
performance of their business right now.
And I call this the finger on the pulse.
For me, as most business
that I win this month will not trickle
into
next month.
We get maybe a couple of people split
payments, but the majority of
them won't.
If I take a year's worth of earnings right
now, I'm not going to be
marketing very hard because I'm going to
be lulled into a false sense of security
that my business is performing better than
I think it is.
So you stop marketing,
but it takes three months for
that lull to catch up and you
go, "Holy shit, where's all the leads?
I've got no one booked in on calls."
And it's because the mentor didn't really
give
a fuck.
They've got the marketable segment of your
business now.
They're proclaiming to their audience How
to get from 2K to 25K a month,
join my program.
But those people never come back,
never came back.
Yes, your margins were massive, great.
But to extrapolate people's problems in
this manner, to me, is immoral and just
goes against my ethics.
It's personal training, mate.
And I'm sorry,
but I do think your ego needs to come down
a little bit.
It's fucking workouts
and it's chatting to people.
And there are some of you that
are dieticians and nutritionists,
and you're doing
great things with many people.
But since the arrival of GLP-1s,
here's the segment
of people that we used to work with.
Here's the people where critical quality
of life,
longevity, will die in the next 10 years.
They're not your problem anymore.
GLP-1s and the doctors, Mounjaos,
can take them.
The people we are left with in our market
is people that need structure and
motivation.
That's it.
If they have an eating disorder,
should be working with a specialist.
If they are chronically obese,
they should be on GLP-1s.
The people right now that
are perfect for you,
just need a program and some kind of
dietary structure,
need someone to chat to.
They don't even fucking need a weekly
check-in. You don't want to do it.
They don't want it.
It's an hour you could shave away from the
whole process,
again,
which is going to help you scale your
business.
The main premise of all of this is,
if there is a return on investment for
your
customer,
charge them whatever the fuck you want
because they can see that money
back and they're not paying for it their
businesses.
But to do this in personal training in a
service-based industry, ridiculous.
Quick one, talking of low ticket,
in London, September the 5th and
the 6th, which is Saturday and Sunday,
I'm doing an ultra-low ticket
day where I've hired a massive room,
big venue. I want you to come along.
It's a two-day event. Saturday
is going to be more fast-fire, big shows.
Sunday's going to be more intimate.
Tickets start from, I think £35.
And I want you to come along to it.
There's going to be a link in the
description
with more information if you're in London.
If you give me a day or
if you give me two,
I think I can drastically change the
trajectory of your business. And if not,
I'll give you your fucking money back.
So the two main premises here,
monthly recurring revenue, paid in full.
I did a video about this a couple of days
ago saying that, "Hey guys,
you're ripping people off." A lot of
people got defensive.
People said,
"I need paid in full because I need the
money to
spend on ads." Again, James Smith Academy,
eight figures, never got paid ads to
work, never, because our margins
were too small.
We just focused on organic, and it worked.
But here's the thing
that a lot of people aren't telling you,
the ones that are
telling you you need margins to pay ads.
Paid ads work better with organic.
This channel, this business,
business mentorship, James Smith,
Blue Head, the
reason my ads crush
and I triple my money with most of what I
spend is
because it's partnered with loads of
organic content going out on a weekly
basis.
If it was just paid ads,
why the fuck do you think I'm here talking
to you right
now?
The reason I'm so proactive with this type
of content
is it bolsters my paid ads. Not only that,
I get to
understand what an audience wants from an
organic perspective so that my paid stuff
works better. Now, this morning,
someone said,
@coach_akos, "Someone pays or
pay in full, they
are financially incentivized at a much
higher percentage to
execute to higher levels." This
is not you saying this, this
is your business
mentor.
"Paid in full equals better results.
Monthly is dipping your toe in
and never fully committing." This is
bullshit lingo you've got from your coach.
And I replied to it and I said, "Look,
I am not against paid in
full, but for coaching,
I think it's fucked."
And I'll give you some reasons.
Number one, paid in full benefits you,
not your client.
Not your client, ever. You say commitment,
but really, I
guarantee, Coach fucking Akos,
if I went into your life, "Hey, do
you pay for Netflix paid in full?" "No,
I pay monthly." "Oh,
do you pay for Spotify
annually?" "No, I pay monthly." Oh,
when you join my fucking mentorship,
you're the one begging for a split pay.
Why? It's not cost, it's cash flow.
So why is it in your life you don't like
fucking paying for anything up front and
you use PayPal pay in full, but why
is it in your client's life they've got to
pay
you in full for commitment? This
is bullshit double standards.
It's fucked and you know it.
Everything that you proclaim as a
business, me, me,
me, me, me,
everything you build should be client
fucking centric.
It should be about making it easier for
them.
And here's the reality, I'm sorry,
Coach Akos.
If you did weekly or monthly,
you'll benefit your client more,
you'll get way more
sales from it,
and you want them to be able to dip their
toe.
That's a good thing because a lot of the
market will not commit to six
months because not cash, not always cash,
because they think
you're fucking shit at what you do.
And sometimes people want to try before
they buy.
Now,
if someone dips their toe for a month
and leaves, you think it's commitment.
No, I'm sorry.
You're just shit at your job. I'm sorry.
You talked a big game, they bought it,
and it was shit. Do you know how I know?
Because if it was good, and it
was as good as they thought [chuckles] it
was going
to be, they would've stayed.
They would've fucking stayed.
You can't argue with that.
Do you think the people joined and it
was really good
and they left? What the fuck
is wrong with you, brother?
Now,
I love paid in full for my business
mentorship.
I do because I know the value
that I'm giving people.
I think it's worth it.
I think the return will come in three
months, yet I give them 12, and if that
doesn't happen,
I give the fucking money back.
And we can tangibly quantify
that metric because it's called
cash.
It's difficult in your realm as a coach
because the tangibles are
difficult. It can be subjective.
It could be fat loss,
it could be weight lifted,
it could be muscle growth, whatever it is.
But they're very subjective,
whereas mine are objective,
so that's why I go for
paid in full.
But paid in full isn't always the best.
For case in point, Noatonic.
I would much rather someone pays us £50 a
month for fucking ages than they do a £250
order and never come back
again.
Even with the paid in full Noatonic,
they will come back because it will run
out and they'll want more
and it's better than everything else in
the market.
But here's another consideration.
When you do these high ticket programs
and you overcharge people, which you do,
there is an end date. Now,
the problem about having an end date like
that for your
coaching services is
when you rip people off,
they're going to squeeze the fucking
life out of you.
They're going to turn up to check-ins
when they don't want to turn
up to check-ins because they're going to
divide the amount they paid by the amount
of weeks they've got, and they go,
"This check-in's cost me £172.
I will lose out if I don't jump on this
call." Whereas if you charge less, "Hey,
anything I can help with this week?" "No,
I'm good.
Thank you." And there's an element of
scale to that.
So when we charge people a bit less,
and when I did charge people a bit less, I
could be more chill with them. "Hey,
Sophie, anything I need this week?"
"Hey, James. Adapting to the program,
going well.
If you could give me some ideas for
recipes thereafter,
that'd be great." Another
client, "Hey, John,
anything I can help with?" "I'm actually
on holiday this week.
Can we check in next week?" "Cool."
They're paying me £45 a week online,
which I
know doesn't seem like a lot,
but £45 to them was enough for them to go,
"Oh, I'm
going on holiday Tell you what,
I would even say, "Hey, John,
I'm happy to push out
that payment. We can skip a payment
if you want, or I can refund you next week
because you're on holiday." They would
come back and say, "Hey, don't worry about
it.
I know you've got bills to pay." Because
it's a chill amount.
If that was £180 for a week,
they'd be like, "Yes, please.
Refund that." Or they would cancel it
when they go on holiday, and then
they never come back.
Monthly recurring revenue works better for
James Smith
Academy.
It's why we're still making money after
not promoting for nearly a year.
Monthly recurring revenue,
better for Nutonic.
Not to mention,
when we do rounds in investor decks
and we send them to people,
by the way,
we're about to announce a valuation north
of 100 million,
and the amount of subscriptions we have
is often valued more than
the amount of one-off purchases we have.
And again,
don't listen to everything I say about
fucking running a business
or brand.
Not like one of my coaching apps
was one of the biggest ever, and the
ones bigger than me. Adam Sullivan,
high ticket? No monthly recurring revenue.
Kayla Itsines, high ticket?
No monthly recurring revenue. Joe Wicks,
high ticket?
No monthly recurring revenue.
You fucking get the point here, cunts.
I am not saying be cheap, but I am saying
don't be retardedly expensive.
Let me prove my point.
This is an iPhone cable.
If I don't need one,
I don't particularly care.
But that cable breaks,
I'm going to need to buy another one.
Now,
I'm not going to buy a cheap one because
it will more than likely be shit.
And if there's one for $3, $8, $9,
and $19.99, I'm
probably buying the $19.99.
That's premium pricing.
I want a good cable. But
if there's one for $109, I'm going to go,
"Fuck that,
that's fucking ridiculous." You could say,
"But you want to know the
benefits?" No, fuck off, twat.
And by the way, the knife/fork thing,
basically, here it is,
and you'll never be the same in life.
So let's say you're having sushi,
chopsticks, right hand, food to the mouth.
Soup, right hand to the mouth. Let's say
carrot cake, dessert, fork,
right hand to the mouth.
Right hand brings food to your mouth.
When you bring a knife in,
you motherfucker, swap round.
That's mental.
Look, ultimately, for a lot of you,
if you want to go high ticket, it's not
scalable because you need to be the thing.
No one's going to be happy paying three
times the average for the services and be
given some random fucking twat.
They're not.
So you've just got an unscalable business.
It's never going to be a lifestyle
business because you're going to have to
be
every single element of that.
Unfortunately, you think these opinions
are your own, but they
are from the people
that you learnt from who are
trying to use you as a puppet to market
their businesses.
The thing that I said before is,
as a coach,
you should structure everything with
your clients' best interests.
The people above you
are not putting your best
interests because they're thinking about
their marketing.
Now, the crazy thing here is
a lot of you coaches watching this,
you're very good at what you do.
You're very good at communicating,
very good at content.
The business coaches you have
are fucking retards.
They're not that good at social organic
content. I know them.
So the only way for them to scale their
business is to charge you fuckers
fuckloads of money because they can't go
wider than that.
They're shit at making content.
They're not creative.
They're fucking dinosaurs.
If you want 100K months,
you need to grow your personal brand
and your
audience. Daniel Priestley,
seven hours of content, four different
platforms, 11 touch points. And
if you want to have 100K months
on a small following,
you're fucking delusional, mate.
About 1% of your audience will do business
with you at any given point.
The easiest, lowest hanging fruit
is to grow the fucking thing you're
working
on and to do the ultra-low ticket plays
like the book deals.
I'm going to try and sell Nutonic for a
billion dollars.
It is not from people spending £1,000 on a
fucking Nutonic order.
It's from them getting in a habit of every
morning they go via Sainsbury's to the
co-working space to work,
and they buy one can of Nutonic every
single day, and
I make fucking 10p on each one,
which we don't.
It could be even less than that.
That is how I win. Thousands,
tens of thousands,
hundreds of thousands of
people making one small repeat purchase
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday,
Thursday, Friday. That
is how we get to a billion fucking
dollars.
And it's going to take you a few years.
And when I'm there on my fucking yacht
and I said to you, "Don't charge people
£1,000 a fucking month for your shit,"
then it will finally click and you will
fucking realize. You are not
that good at what you
do to charge what you're thinking of
charging.
Instead, stay grounded,
widen your audience,
grow, and build your personal brand.
If you're good enough to be charging
$1,000 a month,
you're selling yourself short
giving people this much of your time
and attention. Has
that ever occurred to you?
If you're that fucking good to charge
that much, why build a prison
that you can't
escape?
Because that's what you're doing with
high-ticket coaching.
Hope you enjoyed that video.
If you want me to ruffle even more
feathers, YouTube
recommends you watch this one here.